ifood.tv 2019-07-11

# Future Today Inc.

  * __**Privacy Policy General**
  * __**Privacy Policy Kids**

Effective date: May 25, 2018 Future Today Inc. ("us", "we", or "our") operates website, mobile applications, OTT applications, and Connected TV applications (the "Service"). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data. We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions.

### Definitions

#### Personal Data

Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession). 

#### Usage Data

Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit). 

#### Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of data stored on your device (computer or mobile device). 

#### Data Controller

Data Controller means the natural or legal person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal information are, or are to be, processed. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your Personal Data. 

#### Data Processors (or Service Providers)

Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller. We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively. 

#### Data Subject (or User)

Data Subject is any living individual who is using our Service and is the subject of Personal Data. 

### Information Collection and Use

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you. 

#### Types of Data Collected

#### Personal Data

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to: 

  * Email address
  * First name and last name
  * Cookies and Usage Data

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send. 

#### Usage Data

We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service or when you access the Service by or through a mobile device ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data. When you access the Service by or through a mobile device, this Usage Data may include information such as the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser you use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data. 

#### Tracking Cookies Data

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information. Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service. 

#### Examples of Cookies we use:

  * Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
  * Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
  * Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
  * Advertising Cookies. Advertising Cookies are used to serve you with advertisements that may be relevant to you and your interests.

#### Use of Data

Future Today Inc. uses the collected data for various purposes: 

  * To provide and maintain our Service
  * To notify you about changes to our Service
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
  * To provide customer support
  * To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
  * To monitor the usage of our Service
  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues
  * To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information

### Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), Future Today Inc. legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it. Future Today Inc. may process your Personal Data because: 

  * We need to perform a contract with you
  * You have given us permission to do so
  * The processing is in our legitimate interests and it's not overridden by your rights
  * To comply with the law

### Retention of Data

Future Today Inc. will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies. Future Today Inc. will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

### Transfer of Data

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction. If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. Future Today Inc. will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

### Disclosure of Data

Business Transaction If Future Today Inc. is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy. Disclosure for Law Enforcement Under certain circumstances, Future Today Inc. may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency). Legal Requirements Future Today Inc. may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * To comply with a legal obligation
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of Future Today Inc.
  * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
  * To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
  * To protect against legal liability

### Security of Data

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### "Do Not Track" Signals

We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked. You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

### Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. Future Today Inc. aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us at admin@ifood.tv.

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights: 

  * The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you. Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.
  * The right of rectification. You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.
  * The right to object. You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.
  * The right of restriction. You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.
  * The right to data portability. You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.
  * The right to withdraw consent. You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where Future Today Inc. relied on your consent to process your personal information.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests. You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA). 

### Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. We may allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within our services. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send the advertisements and links that appear on our site and apps. We do not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

#### Analytics

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service. 

##### Google Analytics

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy Terms web page: <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>

##### Mixpanel

Mixpanel is provided by Mixpanel Inc You can prevent Mixpanel from using your information for analytics purposes by opting-out. To opt-out of Mixpanel service, please visit this page: <https://mixpanel.com/optout/> For more information on what type of information Mixpanel collects, please visit the Terms of Use page of Mixpanel: <https://mixpanel.com/terms/>

#### Advertising

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Service. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) .

### Links to Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

### Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important to us. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 16. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers. Under 16 viewers must use the Future Today Inc. sites under adult supervision.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us: **By email: admin@ifood.tv**

This Privacy Statement applies to the web sites and applications targeted to kids below 13 years by Future Today Inc.(collectively, “we”, “our”, or “us”). This Privacy Statement governs your use of our Sites and Apps, regardless of how you access or use them. By “Sites”, we mean any website or URL of ours that we have linked to this Privacy Statement and all features, applications, content, and downloads that are operated by us and that are available through the Sites, and by “Mobile Apps” and “Apps”, we mean our products and services that we make available via mobile telecommunications platforms and/or through social networking platforms or app stores, if you are visiting the Sites, please also review the Sites’ Term of Service. 

### Children

WE DO NOT KNOWINGLY COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN UNDER 13.   We take many special precautions to protect the privacy of children under 13. 

  * At our websites and through our apps intended for children, we do not collect personal contact information (like full name, birthdate, phone number or home address) from children without the consent of a parent or legal guardian, except in limited circumstances authorized by law. 
  * We collect some information (like IP address, mobile device UDID, operating system, etc.) automatically and use technology like cookies to provide functionality and support our operations. 
  * We do not ask for more personal information than is necessary for a child to view our videos. 
  * We take steps to prevent children from posting or publicly disclosing personal contact information. 
  * Parents can ask us to update or delete their children’s information. 

We use technology, like cookies, to recognize visitors by their user name when they revisit our Site and to screen for age in accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”). We may also use technology for similar purposes in our Apps. 

We also use technology to recognize returning visitors, for research, and for other purposes, including to screen under-age visitors from certain features or areas intended for older visitors, and to collect certain information automatically. We require our advertising service partners to comply with self-regulatory guidelines on targeted advertising. We do not permit interest-based advertising on Sites directed to children under 13 or where we have actual knowledge that a child is under 13. 

### WHAT WE COLLECT – ADULTS AND TEENS

We sometimes collect information from adults and teens to serve your needs, manage our content and advertising, operate efficiently, and improve our products and services. 

  * We may collect personal contact information, like e-mail address from consumers 13 or older when voluntarily submitted. 
  * Registration may be required to use some Sites, services or Apps. 
  * We may obtain information from commercial sources and combine it with information we have collected. 
  * Certain information may be collected automatically at our Sites or Apps, like your IP address, UDID, browser setting, operating system, referring domain, language preferences, mobile carrier if you are using a mobile device, general location (e.g., zip code, but not specific address without consent) and other information. 
  * Third parties may also collect certain information via our Sites or Apps. 

#### COOKIES AND TECHNOLOGY

  * Our Sites, services and Apps use technology, like cookies and web beacons, to manage registrations or access to certain features, store your settings and preferences, conduct age-screening, offer you personalized content, shop, help us understand the features that appeal to visitors, and manage advertising, among other things. 
  * We also work with third parties who offer analytics or deliver targeted ads online or through Apps. They use technology and collect device identifiers, such as your IP address or mobile UDID, and information on your activities, to do so. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads but will still see ads, although they may be less relevant to you. 
  * Tools are available to help you control some of these technologies. 
  * Future Today Inc and its agents or service providers or business partners may receive and store certain information automatically when you visit our Sites, use an online service or download or use a mobile App. This may include information on your browser type and operating system, the pages that you view, referring sites (sites you visited before you came to our site and sites you go to after you visit our site), IP addresses, or unique device identifiers associated with mobile devices, smart phones, etc. This information allows us to count the total number of “hits” on our Sites or installation and frequency of use of our Apps. 
  * We collect certain information using technology, like cookies and pixel tags. 
  * Third party analytics and advertising networks also use cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, clear GIFs and other technology to collect certain information automatically. Advertising networks may use this information to serve you targeted ads for products and services that, based on your activities, are likely to be of interest to you (“interest-based advertising”). We do not permit interest-based advertising on Sites directed to children under 13 or where we have actual knowledge that a child is under 13. 
  * Other business partners, like social media sites, may also use cookies and similar technology to collect certain information about your visits to our Sites through social media plug-ins. You may have the option to log in to one of our websites using your social media user name and password; if so, the social media operator (e.g., Facebook, YouTube, Twitter, etc.) may be able to link your activities at our Site to your registration information. 
  * Find out more about these technologies and how you can control their use below. 

### Cookies

A “cookie” is a small file that does not contain personally identifiable information and is saved on your computer or mobile device. Cookies help improve your user experience, and allow us to analyze our Sites and Apps and manage our advertising.

  * Our cookies help to give you faster access to pages you have already visited; they allow you to personalize your pages and us to customize our offerings; and they help you to participate in some activities or events on our Sites. For instance, some of our Sites have scavenger or treasure hunts, and we need to use cookies to keep track of your progress. If you leave our Site and then return, cookies will tell us what things you have already collected so that you do not have to start all over again. Cookies can also keep track of items in your shopping cart and wish list in our online stores, and may be used to help you engage in other activities, like comparison shopping. 
  * We also use cookies to help us figure out how many people visit our Sites, which of our Web pages they go to and how long they stay there. This information helps us figure out which of our Web features are successes and what Sites might need improvement. For administrative purposes, we collect IP addresses. Certain Internet service providers may assign the same IP address to many users. The IP address allows us to count the total number of “hits” on our sites. Your IP address and cookies are not connected to any personally identifiable or online contact information, like a name or email address, unless you register or order at our online stores; however, if you register at our online stores, all information we collect will be associated with your customer file. 
  * You can set your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent or turn off all cookies through your Internet browser (e.g., Internet Explorer or Safari). Check your browser’s Help menu or your built-in mobile device settings to find out how. Some mobile devices store cookies not only in areas connected to the browser, but also in areas that are app-specific so these cookies cannot be controlled by the browser settings. Check your app settings options on your mobile device to find out how to manage or delete cookies that may be stored in these other areas. 
  * Please note that if you do not accept cookies, some features or activities may not be available to you. 

#### Web Beacons, Pixel tags or clear GIFs

We also use other technology, called web beacons, pixel tags or clear GIFs, to provide us with other important anonymous information, such as when an e-mail has been opened. Companies that advertise on our Sites may also place web beacons in their ads to help develop statistics on the effectiveness of advertising at our Sites. We do not control web beacons in third party ads.

  * **Apps**

When downloading an App (or using an App that relies on online features made available through your mobile platform), the app store will collect certain device and app-related information. We do not control the data collection or privacy practices of those stores. You should review the privacy policy and terms of use of any mobile application store before downloading or using any app and review and use available controls and settings on your device to reflect your preferences. 

  * **Location Information**

For some Apps or services, we or our third party service and content providers and analytics companies may collect location information, including location information provided either by a mobile device interacting with one of our Apps or associated with your IP address or WiFi network. These features might enable you to engage in activities like find a nearby store or play certain games, for example. You can generally limit or prohibit the collection of location information by using the built-in settings on your mobile device. You will typically be notified if the App or service collects location information and given a chance to agree. We do not permit collection of precise location information (actual address) in mobile Apps without your consent. Child-directed Apps do not collect precise location information.

  * **Website and Mobile App Analytics**

We or our agents and service partners may use cookies and web beacons to analyze the effectiveness of our Sites, services and Apps. This typically involves collecting your IP address or UDID and information on your activities, like the sites you visit or frequency of use of an App. We require these providers to commit to maintaining the anonymity of this information. You may be able to opt out of data collection or use by some third party analytics companies who work with us. Contact us if you would like information on our third party analytics service providers.

  * **Targeted Advertising**

Future Today Inc Apps may work with third party online or mobile network advertisers that use cookies, pixels, or transparent GIF files to help us manage advertising at our Sites or Apps intended for people over the age of 13, and measure its effectiveness. GIF files enable third party ad networks to recognize a unique cookie on your Web browser or mobile device. The cookie may be placed by us, or by another advertiser that works with our third party network advertiser. The information that we collect and share in this fashion is de-identified and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address. However, it may keep track of the sites you have visited that are associated with the ad network. This information may be used for the purpose of targeting advertisements on our Sites and other sites based on those interests, and to learn which ads bring users to our Sites. Please note: your opt-out choices are browser-specific and device-specific.

  * **Social Media Platforms and Plugins**

If you are a member of a social media network, like Facebook, a cookie may be sent to that network when you access a page of our Site or an App that links to their website through a plugin (such as Facebook’s “Like” or Google “+1” buttons), register or log into your account at their platform, or use your social media user name and password to log into our Site where you have the option to do so. That may enable them and us to link your activities with your personal registration information at their site, and may include notifying your friends or connections about your activities at our Site, and using tracking technologies to monitor your online activities in order to serve targeted ads. The social media networks’ privacy policy and terms apply to your use of their platforms. Your browser or device may allow you to block these technologies but you should visit the third party website and review their privacy policy and your registration profile or account to find out your options. 

### CHOICES

We respect your choices about receiving promotional offers and updates from us.

### APP CONTROLS

Your device may allow you to block or manage push notifications, location information, in-app purchases, or ability to access the web.

### SHARING

We may share information:

  * Within our family of companies, and with our agents and service providers. 
  * As necessary to satisfy a legal request, protect property or personal safety, when a business is bought or sold, or as otherwise allowed or required by law. 

### LINKS

Our Sites or Apps may link to or use other content from the Internet, including content offered by third parties that we do not control and whose privacy and data collection practices may differ from ours. Your computer or mobile device settings may allow you to block or partially block web access, but those settings may not be effective in all cases. 

### OTHER IMPORTANT INFORMATION

**Security**

We strive to maintain the security of information but cannot guarantee that information security measures are fail-safe

**OUR LOCATION; DATA TRANSFERS**

This Site and the servers that make this Site available may not be located in your country of residence and are governed by U.S. laws. By using this Site, you agree to the transfer, collection, processing and use of data by this Site and us. This Site, the servers that make this Site available, and databases where we house information may not be located in your country of residence, and applicable privacy laws may differ. However, we take reasonable steps to safeguard personal information as outlined in this Privacy Statement. By using this Site, you agree to the transfer, collection, processing and use of data as set forth in this Privacy Statement, our Terms and Conditions, and any other terms provided at the time of collection. However related to mobile apps, the servers that store the data will be of the respective platforms.

**Updates**

We will update this Privacy Statement from time to time by posting the updated Privacy Statement online. We will not change how we handle previously collected information without providing notice.

**CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

If you are a resident of California, you have certain rights. Under California Civil Code § 1798.83, California residents have the right to receive, once a year, information about third parties with whom we have shared information about you for their marketing purposes during the previous calendar year, and a description of the categories of personal information shared. To make such a request, please send an email to biz@ifood.tv we will respond to you within 30 days of receiving such a request.

### QUESTIONS

We strive always to be transparent and clear about our policies. Please contact us at [biz@ifood.tv](mailto:biz@ifood.tv) if you have questions

### A SPECIAL NOTE FOR PARENTS AND LEGAL GUARDIANS:

Future Today Inc adheres to the U.S. Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”) and the guidelines of the Children’s Advertising Review Unit (“CARU”) of the Council of Better Business Bureaus, Inc. in our web Sites, online services and Apps directed to children under 13. Wherever we refer to “children” or a “child” in this Privacy Statement, we mean children under 13. Please help us protect your children’s privacy by instructing them never to provide personal information (like their full name, e-mail address, home address, telephone number, etc.) without your permission.
